questionSet = [
    {"question": "Which basketball player had a nickname 'Black Mamba'?", "A": "a) Derrick Rose, ", "B": "b) Kobe Bryant, ",
     "C": "c) Michael Jordan, ", "D": "d) LeBron James ", "rightAnswer": "B", "lifelineAudience": "a) 25% b) 50% c) 5% d) 20%"},
    {"question": "Who has a nickname 'The Logo'?", "A": "a) Michael Jordan, ", "B": "b) Jerry West, ", "C": "c) Allen Iverson, ",
     "D": "d) Luc Longley, ", "rightAnswer": "B", "lifelineAudience": "a) 30% b) 50% c) 0% d) 20%"},
    {"question": "What is the all time scoring record?", "A": "a) 81, ", "B": "b) 100, ", "C": "c) 69, ",
     "D": "d) 89, ", "rightAnswer": "B", "lifelineAudience": "a) 15% b) 60% c) 25% d) 20%"},
    {"question": "What is 'airball'? ", "A": "a) game without dribble, ", "B": "b) a ball with a lot of air, ", "C": "c) a shot, which does not touch the rim, ",
     "D": "d) brand of a basketball gear, ", "rightAnswer": "C", "lifelineAudience": "a) 15% b) 5% c) 60% d) 20%"},
    {"question": "Is it allowed to score 5 points in one shot?", "A": "a) yes, ", "B": "b) only in 4th quarter,", "C": "c) no,",
     "D": "d) only after the foul", "rightAnswer": "C", "lifelineAudience": "a) 10% b) 20% c) 50% d) 10%"},
    {"question": "Who invented basketball?", "A": "a) James Naismith, ", "B": "b) Napoleon Bonaparte,", "C": "c) Michael Jordan, ",
     "D": "d) George Karl", "rightAnswer": "A", "lifelineAudience": "a) 70% b) 0% c) 5% d) 25%"},
    {"question": "'White Men Can't Jump' is: ", "A": "a) a truth, ", "B": "b) a joke,", "C": "c) a basketball movie,",
     "D": "d) a medical statement", "rightAnswer": "C", "lifelineAudience": "a) 30% b) 5% c) 60% d) 5%"},
    {"question": "What is a Kobe Bryant scoring record?", "A": "a) 100, ", "B": "b) 81,", "C": "c) 69, ",
     "D": "d) 69", "rightAnswer": "B", "lifelineAudience": "a) 3% b) 67% c) 16% d) 14%"},
    {"question": "How many NBA Champions titles does the Chicago Bulls have?", "A": "a) 3, ", "B": "b) 4, ", "C": "c) 5,",
     "D": "d) 6", "rightAnswer": "D", "lifelineAudience": "a) 10% b) 20% c) 25% d) 55%"},
    {"question": "Which coach has the most NBA Champion titles? ", "A": "a) Pat Riley, ", "B": "b) Phil Jackson,", "C": "c) Bill Russel, ",
     "D": "d) Chuck Daly", "rightAnswer": "B", "lifelineAudience": "a) 16% b) 52% c) 24% d) 8%"},
    {"question": "Which player is called 'The Chosen One'? ", "A": "a) Michael Jordan, ", "B": "b) Kobe Bryant,", "C": "c) Kareem Abdul - Jabbar, ",
     "D": "d) Lebron James", "rightAnswer": "D", "lifelineAudience": "a) 16% b) 14% c) 25% d) 45%"},
    {"question": "In which year Lebron James won his first NBA title? ", "A": "a) 2011, ", "B": "b) 2012,", "C": "c) 2013, ",
     "D": "d) 2014", "rightAnswer": "B", "lifelineAudience": "a) 16% b) 52% c) 24% d) 8%"},
    {"question": "Which player was called 'The Glove'? ", "A": "a) Dikembe Mutombo, ", "B": "b) Hakeem Olajuwon,", "C": "c) Gary Payton, ",
     "D": "d) Shaquille O'Neal", "rightAnswer": "C", "lifelineAudience": "a) 16% b) 14% c) 45% d) 25%"},
    {"question": "Which player was called 'The Dream'? ", "A": "a) Michael Jordan, ", "B": "b) Hakeem Olajuwon,", "C": "c) Magic Johnson, ",
     "D": "d) Karl Malone", "rightAnswer": "B", "lifelineAudience": "a) 18% b) 52% c) 14% d) 16%"},
    {"question": "Which player had a famous interview about practice? ", "A": "a) Michael Jordan, ", "B": "b) Gilbert Arenas,", "C": "c) Luka Doncic, ",
     "D": "d) Allen Iverson", "rightAnswer": "D", "lifelineAudience": "a) 11% b) 29% c) 23% d) 37%"},
    {"question": "He was the MVP of the 2010 regular season: ", "A": "a) Kobe Bryant, ", "B": "b) Paul Pierce,", "C": "c) Lebron James, ",
     "D": "d) Kevin Durant", "rightAnswer": "C", "lifelineAudience": "a) 20% b) 15% c) 43% d) 22%"},
    {"question": "He made 23 924 rebound during his whole NBA career: ", "A": "a) Kareem Abdul Jabbar, ", "B": "b) Moses Malone,", "C": "c) Wilt Chamberlain, ",
     "D": "d) Bill Russell", "rightAnswer": "C", "lifelineAudience": "a) 22% b) 18% c) 44% d) 36%"},
    {"question": "Who has a triple - double games record? ", "A": "a) Oscar Robertson, ", "B": "b) Magic Johnson,", "C": "c) Jason Kidd, ",
     "D": "d) Russell Westbrook", "rightAnswer": "D", "lifelineAudience": "a) 28% b) 12% c) 16% d) 44%"},
    {"question": "He was the smallest player in NBA history:  ", "A": "a) Spud Webb, ", "B": "b) Allen Iverson,", "C": "c) Muggsy Bogues, ",
     "D": "d) Baron Davis", "rightAnswer": "C", "lifelineAudience": "a) 40% b) 7% c) 43% d) 10%"},
    {'question': 'Who is the all time scorer in NBA history?', 'A': 'a) Michael Jordan,', 'B': 'b) Kobe Bryant,', 'C': 'c) Kareem Abdul - Jabbar,',
    'D': 'd) Lebron James', 'rightAnswer': 'D', 'lifelineAudience': 'a) 4% b) 16% c) 9% d) 71%'},
    {'question': 'Which team holds the record for most NBA championships won?', 'A': 'a) Chicago Bulls,', 'B': 'b) Los Angeles Lakers,', 'C': 'c) Boston Celtics,',
      'D': 'd) Golden State Warriors', 'rightAnswer': 'C', 'lifelineAudience': 'a) 6% b) 40% c) 46% d) 8%'},
    {'question': 'Who was the first player to be drafted straight out from high school into the NBA?', 'A': 'a) Kobe Bryant,', 'B': 'b) Lebron James,',
      'C': 'c) Kevin Garnett,', 'D': 'd) Tracy McGrady', 'rightAnswer': 'C', 'lifelineAudience': 'a) 18% b) 36% c) 40% d) 6%'},
    {'question': 'What is the name of the annual NBA event in which teams select new players from college and international leagues?', 'A': 'a) NBA Draft Lottery',
      'B': 'b) NBA Combine', 'C': 'c) NBA Draft', 'D': 'd) NBA Summer League', 'rightAnswer': 'C', 'lifelineAudience': 'a) 13% b) 6% c) 50% d) 31%'},
    {'question': 'Who was the tallest player in NBA history?', 'A': 'a) Manute Bol,', 'B': "b) Shaquille O'Neal,", 'C': 'c) Yao Ming,',
       'D': 'd) Tacko Fall', 'rightAnswer': 'A', 'lifelineAudience': 'a) 33% b) 17% c) 30% d) 20%'},
    {'question': 'What is a regulation height of a basketball hoop?', 'A': 'a) 9 feet (2,74 meters),', 'B': 'b) 10 feet (3,05 meters),', 'C': 'c) 11 feet (3,35 meters),',
      'D': 'd) 12 feet (3,66 meters)', 'rightAnswer': 'B', 'lifelineAudience': 'a) 14% b) 46% c) 22% d) 18%'}
]
